As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is high school baseball!
!مسرح اليوم هو كرة قاعدة مدارس ثانوية
A thin line separates outs and safes!
!"خطّ رفيع يفصل بين "آمن" و"خارج
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The Shredded Championship Flag Case.
قضيّة علم البطولة المُمزق
Beika High Shuko Academy
ثانويّة بيكا أكاديمية شوكو
Come on, you can do it!
!هيّا يا بيكا! أنتم لها يا بيكا
Hey, I can't hear you!
!صوتكم منخفض
They won't win unless you cheer louder!
!لن يفوزوا ما لم تهتفوا بصوتٍ أعلى
Dad! This isn't like pro baseball!
!أبي! هذا ليس ككرة قاعدة المحترفين
Send that ball flying!
!اضربها! أرسل تلك الكرة في الهواء
Why did he come to cheer for his bartender's son?
كنتُ لأفهم لو كانت ثانويّة تيتان، لكن لمَ أتى لتشجيع مدرسة ابن ساقي الحانة التي يرتادها؟
Besides, there's no point with such a one-sided game...
كما أنّها مباراة من طرف واحد، لا معنى للتشجيع
Shuko's pitcher sure is good, though.
لكنّ رامي شوكو بارع حقّاً
Strike two!
!رمية ثانية
Strike three! You're out!
!رمية ثالثة! خرج حامل المضرب
Strike!
!رمية
Strike two!
!رمية ثانية
Strike three! You're out!
!رمية ثالثة! خرج حامل المضرب
You're so cute, Kaji-kun!
!أنتَ ظريف يا كاجي-كن
Whose side are you on?!
في أيّ جانب أنتِ يا سونوكو؟
But he's just so cute!
لكنّه ظريفٌ جدّاً
Really? Let me see!
حقّاً؟ دعيني أرى
This could be a good game!
قد تكون مباراةً جيّدة
Hey, now...
...أنت
Plus his dad's a doctor and he's the school's best student!
كما أنّ أباه طبيب وهو أكثر التلامذة !تفوّقاً في مدرسته
Too good to pass up!
!لا يمكن تفويته
Say, didn't Shuko win the district championship last year?
أخبريني، ألم تفز أكاديمية شوكو حببطولة المحافظة العام الفائت؟
Yep! They're looking to win it this year too!
بلى، إنّهم المُفضّلون للفوز هذا العام أيضاً
They've got such a great pitcher!
ألا تسمع هتافهم هناك؟
But when did Shuko get so good?
لكن متى كانت شوكو بهذه القوّة؟
It all thanks to Kaji-kun!
هذا بفضل كاجي-كن
The current headmaster founded it way back when
أسّسها رجل ثريّ رفيع المقام في الماضي كمعهدٍ متحفّظ
as a prestigious prep school.
ولا يزال رئيس مجلس إدارتها للآن
But its image suddenly changed when Kaji-kun showed up!
لكنّ صورتها تغيّرت تماماً عندما ظهر كاجي-كن
You sure know a lot!
تعرفين الكثير
I know everything about Kaji-kun!
!تحقّقتُ من كلّ شيءٍ عن كاجي-كن
What are those people doing?
ماذا يفعل هذان؟
Thanks, Principal!
شكراً حضرة الناظر
Even the principal? Shuko sure has lots of school spirit!
حتّى الناظر موجود للتشجيع؟ أكاديمية شوكو تحمل روحاً بحقّ
Safe!
!آمن
Huh? They're gone.
ماذا؟ اختفيا
Balk! Ball one!
!مخالفة حركة! الكرة الأولى
It's okay, Kaji!
!اهدأ يا كاجي
You can do it!
!لا بأس
Good hit!
!ضربة جيّدة
Kaji-kun...
...كاجي-كن
What happened?
ماذا حصل فجأةً؟
It started after he got that balk call...
...كانت آنذاك، عندما حصل على مخالفة الحركة
It looked like he saw something.
بدا أنّه رأى شيئاً
But what?
ماذا بالضبط؟
What do you think's wrong?
ما خطبه برأيكم؟
Maybe he has a stomachache?
ربما توجعه معدته؟
Who was that?
من كان ذاك؟
Eto-kun, Shuko's former southpaw ace.
إيتو-كن، رامي شوكو الأعسر السابق
But he got suspended for causing trouble
لكنّه فُصل بعد تسبيبه المتاعب
after Kaji-kun stole the spotlight!
!بعدما خطف كاجي-كن الدور الأساسيّ منه
He must've asked to pitch.
طلب أن يأخذ مكان الرامي غالباً
I guess he wasn't allowed...
يبدو أنّه لم يحصل على الموافقة
Of course he wasn't!
بالطبع
Nobody can take Kaji-kun's place!
فلا أحد يستطيع استبدال كاجي-كن
Nurse's Office
مكتب الممرضة
That's it!
!هكذا
This stuff's great!
!لذيذ
Kaji-kun is being mocked...
...لو كان كاجي-كن من يرمي
Oh, come on now...
...سونوكو
Are you serious?!
أحقّاً ذلك؟
I wonder what happened.
أحصل أمرٌ ما؟
That's horrible!
...فظيع
Authorized personnel only!
أنت! لا يُسمح بدخول من لا !يملكون صلاحية
The championship flag was shredded up?!
مُزّق علم البطولة؟
Totally thrashed! Everyone was in a panic!
!قُطّع طرفاً لطرف! كان الجميع في هلع
But who would do that?!
لكن من قد يُقدم على ذلك؟
That's just it...
...في الواقع
Ever since last year's victory,
،منذ فوزنا العام الفائت
we've had all sorts of jealousy-related trouble.
مررنا بالعديد من المضايقات المشحونة بالغيرة
If this was similarly done by an outsider,
،إن كانت هذه الحادثة بفعل دخيل أيضاً
then we're victims, and we can save our school's reputation.
فنحن ضحايا، ويمكننا إنقاذ سمعة مدرستنا بالكاد
But we were still responsible for the flag's safe-keeping.
لكن لا يمكننا التهرّب من فشلنا في المحافظة على العلم المؤتمن لدينا
We have no choice but to drop out of the tournament.
لا خيار أمامنا سوى الانسحاب من المسابقة
That's terrible...
...هذا محزن
Why don't they call the police?
لمَ لم يتّصلوا بالشرطة؟
To save face.
!لحفظ ماء الوجه
They want to figure out if this was
يريدون تحديد إذا ما كان المجرم
an inside or an outside job first.
من الخارج أم الداخل أولاً على الأقل !وضبط وضع المدرسة
I see.
فهمت
Dad, get up! We need you!
!أفق يا أبي! لديك عمل
Huh? I can't drink any more...
...ماذا؟ لم أعد أستطيع الشرب
You can't be serious, Ran...
...ران، أيمكن أنّك تقصدين
Two windows...
نافذتان
One faces the field...
إحداهما تقابل الملعب
Wow! It's like the best seat in the house!
مُذهل! تستطيع المشاهدة كأنّك !في أفضل مقاعد الملعب
Hey, you! This is authorized personnel only!
!أنت! لا يُصرّح الدخول لغير المعنيين
Dad! No violence!
!أبي! بلا عنف
Yeah, yeah...
حسناً، حسناً
And one other window-- What the?!
...والنافذة الأخرى
The window's broken!
!النافذة محطّمة
What's this?
ما هذا؟
There's a ladder leading up to it!
يوجد سلّم يقود لها في الخارج
The culprit snuck in from outside.
تسلّل الفاعل من الخارج
Well done, Mori Kogoro-san!
كما يُتوقع منك أيّها المتحرّي العظيم موري كوغورو-سان
I'm glad I asked you for help!
يسرّني أني طلبت المساعدة منك
But they still have to drop out of the tournament.
لكن لا يزال عليهم الانسحاب من البطولة
Everyone's sad but the principal...
...الجميع مُحبطون، بينما الناظر
Wait a minute! What's this?!
...لحظة، أهذا
He's so useless!
لا فائدة منه
Hey, Mister. Where is that ladder usually at?
أخبرني يا عمّ، أين يكون ذاك السلّم عادةً؟
The storeroom. I have no idea when it was taken.
في المخزن، لا أعلم متى أُخرج
Was the storeroom locked?
أكان المخزن مُقفلاً؟
Actually, the key has been missing all morning.
في الواقع فقدنا المفتاح منذ الصباح
What?!
!ماذا؟
The keys to that office too?!
ماذا؟ مفتاح مكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة أيضاً؟
Yes, they disappeared this morning.
أجل، اختفيا منذ الصباح
I figured as such.
كما ظننت
This was an inside job.
كان الفاعل من الداخل
Come again?!
!ماذا؟
The culprit used the key to enter this office.
استعمل الفاعل المفتاح لدخول هذا المكتب
What about the ladder?!
!ماذا عن السلّم؟
A ruse to make it look
حيلة من تدبير المجرم
like someone snuck in from outside.
لتوهمنا بأنّ شخصاً تسلّل من الخارج
Do you have any proof of that?
ألديك دليل على ذلك؟
Ahh! The floor's covered in glass!
!الأرض مليئة بشظايا الزجاج! لا أستطيع المشي
The floor? That's it!
الأرض؟
Yes. There's broken glass near the window.
أجل، شظايا الزجاج مترامية قرب النافذة
Had the culprit stepped in it,
،لو وطأها الفاعل
glass shards would have lodged in the shoes.
لعلِقت الشظايا بحذائه وانتقلت أثناء مشيه
But the floor is scratch-free.
لكن الأرض خالية من الشظايا هنا
The culprit set the ladder up but didn't enter through the window.
أي أنّ الفاعل وضع السلّم لكنه لم يدخل من النافذة
There was no reason to--
لم تكن هناك حاجة
they had the key to the office.
فمعه مفتاح المكتب
Yeah, now you got it!
أجل، هكذا
Did you want this to be an outside job that badly?
هل أردت أن تكون فعلةً خارجية لهذا الحد؟
I guess it might be natural for any good principal, but...
ربما ذلك طبيعيّ بالنسبة لأيّ ناظر ...يفكّر بسمعة المدرسة، لكن
It would seem this happened during the game.
بناءً على الظروف، فالأرجح أنّ الحادثة وقعت أثناء المباراة
So the culprit wasn't at the game?
أي من لم يتواجد في المباراة يحمل شبهة الفاعل؟
That's right.
أجل
I saw Eto-kun enter the school building...
...المعذرة، رأيتُ إيتو-كن يدخل مبنى المدرسة
So did I!
أجل، كذلك أنا
Stop kidding around!
!يكفي مزاحاً
I did come inside, but I went to the bathroom!
!دخلتُ المبنى بالفعل، لكنّي ذهبت لدورة المياه
Can you prove that?
أيمكنك إثبات ذلك؟
No, but I wasn't the only one inside!
لا أستطيع... لكنّي لم أكن الوحيد في المبنى
Kaji-kun was holding his stomach--
...كان كاجي-كن يمسك بمعدته
That's right! He went to the nurse's office!
صحيح، ذهب لمكتب الممرضة
It was me! I did it!
!كان أنا! أنا الفاعل
You did?!
!أهذه الحقيقة؟
You can't be serious!
!لا يمكن أنّك جاد يا كاجي! يستحيل أنّك فعلتها
I haven't been pitching well lately...
لم أكن أرمي الكرة بمستوى عالٍ مؤخراً
You saw me out there.
ذلك جلّي لكم من مباراة اليوم
I was scared to be in the tournament.
كنتُ أخشى المشاركة في البطولة
His pitching was bad.
كان رميه سيّئاً حقّاً
But he lost his cool only after the 7th-inning balk.
لكنّه فقد تركيزه بعد مخالفة الشوط السابع فقط
And if he didn't wanna play,
،وإذا لم يرد المشاركة
he could've faked an illness.
كان بإمكانه التظاهر بمرض
Would he really shred up the flag and create a ruse?
هل سيمزّق العلم ويبتكر حيلة حقاً؟
Kenya!
!كينيا
Mom!
أمّي
I saw her earlier...
رأيتُها آنذاك
Something's fishy here!
هناك أمرٌ غريب
Why won't they look at each other?!
لمَ يتفاديان نظرات بعضهما؟
It was me! I did it!
!كنتُ أنا! أنا الفاعلة
No, I did it! I have proof!
!كلا! أنا الفاعل! لديّ دليل
Here! I did it with this!
!هذه! فعلتُها بهذه
It's the same fabric as the flag.
إنّه نفس قماش العلم
Kenya!
!كينيا
How could you?!
!كاجي! أيّها الوغد
What were you thinking?!
!كيف لك ذلك؟
Well?
ما الوضع؟
They're deciding whether to call the police or not.
يتناقشون بشأن الاتّصال بالشرطة
Apparently, they need to consult the ailing headmaster.
يبدو أنّ عليهم استشارة رئيس مجلس الإدارة طريح الفراش حالياً
I still can't believe it.
لا أزال عاجزةً عن التصديق
Did he really do it?
أفعلها كاجي-كن حقاً؟
I'm almost certain--
...آنذاك
Yes, Kaji definitely saw someone in the office then.
لا شكّ في الأمر، رأى كاجي شخصاً في مكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة من النافذة وقتها
That's why he pitched poorly and was relieved.
لذا رمى بضعف كي يتمّ إخراجه
Then he went to the nurse's office and the headmaster's office.
ثمّ ذهب لمكتب الممرضة، ومكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة
Hey, Conan-kun! What're you looking at?
كونان-كن! ما الذي تنظر له؟
I don't think we should be doing this...
كونان-كن، لا يجدر بنا فعل هذا
What the?!
...هذا
Aha! So that person did it!
!فهمت الآن، كان هو الفاعل
But I don't understand why...
...لكن لا أفهم دافعه
What was there to gain from this?
ما قد يجني من فعل هذا؟
It's definitely strange, alright.
هذا غريبٌ بحقّ
A friend that goes here told me that even though
...أخبرتني صديقة تدرس هنا
Kaji-kun was likely to help them win again this year,
كانوا المرشّحين المفضّلين للفوز بالبطولة ،الوطنية هذا العام بفضل كاجي-كن
some people were complaining.
لكن كان هناك من يتذمّر رغم ذلك
What?!
!ماذا؟
This used to be a top prep school.
فقد كانت هذه معهداً متحفّظاً
They said that if the team got too good,
قالوا أنّ تفوّق الفريق أكثر سيجذب التلامذة للتشجيع
people wouldn't study as much.
فيقصّرون في الدراسة
That was the headmaster's policy.
كانت هذه سياسة رئيس مجلس الإدارة
He really hates sports.
فهو يكره الرياضة
He insists that they're unnecessary;
كان يقول أنّ هدف المعهد
all he wants is to create notable people like himself.
هو تنشئة شخصيات مرموقة مثله، ولا داعي للمعان الرياضة
He was actually supposed to come today.
كان يُفترض به أن يأتي اليوم
Why didn't he?
ما الذي حصل؟
He was going to announce the team's withdrawal
كان سيعلن انسحاب فريق كرة القاعدة
from the tournament, but with his health failing...
...من البطولة، لكن تدهورت صاحته
That's it! That's the motive!
!فهمت! وجدتُ الدافع
Now I just need the old man's help!
الآن أحتاج مساعدة العمّ مُجدداً فقط
An autograph session for my fans?
جلسة توقيع لمعجبيّ؟
Yeah! Sit over there!
أجل، اجلس هناك
All those girls are waiting!
!كلّ الفتيات في صفوفٍ ينتظرنك
Is it really okay to do this at a school?
لـ-لكن أيصحّ بي أن أقوم بهذا في مدرسة حقّاً؟
Here we go again...
...بلا سابق إنذار مُجدداً
Ahem! This is Mori Kogoro!
أنا موري كوغورو
Can you hear me?
هل تسمعونني؟
Dad?
أبي؟
Would everyone please come to the headmaster's office?
هلّا اجتمعتم في مكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة من فضلكم فوراً؟
I'm about to reveal the truth behind this incident.
سأكشف حقيقة هذه الحادثة
Mori-san! Your work here is over!
!موري-سان، انتهى عملك هنا
If this is about your payment--
...إن كان بهذا بخصوص أجرك
No, I'm not done here;
كلا، لم ينته
the real culprit hasn't been caught yet.
فلم يُقبض على الفاعل الحقيقيّ بعد
The real culprit? Don't be silly.
الفاعل الحقيقيّ؟ لا يُعقل
He's right here!
!إنّه هنا
No, Kaji-kun isn't the one responsible.
كلا، كاجي-كن ليس الفاعل
Then--
...إذاً
Nor is it his mother.
ولا أمّه
Then who?
من إذاً؟
If you purposely cut a flag up,
،إذا قطعت علماً متعمّداً
you'd probably cut the front.
ستقطع المقدّمة في العادة
Ran. Hold the flag up.
ران، ارفعي العلم
Okay.
حسناً
go from the top left to the bottom right.
تمتدّ من أعلى الجانب الأيسر للأيمن السفليّ
The flagpole is on the left, which means...
...عامود العلم على اليسار مما يعني
Ran. Pretend to cut it as if you were the culprit.
ران، تظاهري بالقطع كما لو كنتِ الفاعلة
It's hard to cut!
من الصعب قطعه
Yes. It's hard because you're right-handed.
صحيح، صعبٌ لأنّك تستعملين يدك اليمنى
Ran. Do it as if you were left-handed.
ران، جرّبي كما لو كنتِ عسراء
Like this?
هكذا؟
Yes.
أجل
Cut downward with your left hand,
،اقطعي للأسفل بيدك اليسرى كما لو تحملين الشفرة
as you hold the flag with your right.
بينما تمسكين بالعلم بيمينك
It's easy! And the cuts are the same!
!سهل! والقطع يطابق الآثار
You pitch with your right hand, correct?
أنت ترمي بيدك اليمنى يا كاجي-كن، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
How about you, Eto-kun?
ماذا عنك يا إيتو-كن؟
Eto?!
!إيتو؟
Was it you?!
!أكان أنت إذاً؟
Don't be stupid! Yes, I am a southpaw, but!
...لا-لا تكن أحمق! صحيحٌ أنّي أعسر، لكن
I'm told you're a former ace pitcher.
سمعتُ أنّك النجم السابق
Perhaps you felt there was no point
لعلّك رأيت أنّ لا أهميّة
for the team to play if you couldn't pitch for it.
لمشاركة الفريق إذا لم تلعب معه، فلديك الدافع
No! It wasn't me!
!كـ-كلا! كلا
How could you?!
!إيتو، أيّها الوغد
He's right.
معه حقّ
It wasn't Eto-kun?
لم يكن إيتو-كن يا أبي؟
Have another look at the flag,
،انظري للعلم المقطّع مُجدداً
where the cuts begin.
لموضع بدء التمزيق
Where the cuts begin?
موضع بدء التمزيق؟
Don't they seem a little low?
ألا يبدو منخفضاً كثيراً؟
Had the 180 cm Kaji-kun or Eto-kun cut it,
،لو كان الفاعل كاجي-كن بطول 180 سم أو إيتو-كن
they would've cut from higher up.
لمزّقا من ارتفاعٍ أعلى
But the real culprit couldn't reach the top.
لكنّ الفاعل الحقيقيّ لم يستطع الوصول للأعلى
In other words, the culprit is under 160 cm in height.
ما يعني أنّ طول الفاعل تحت 160 سم
How tall is Kaji-kun's mother?
كم طولك يا أمّ كاجي-كن؟
157 cm.
إنّه 157 سم
But I hear you're right-handed?
لكن سمعت أنّك تستعملين يدك اليمنى
Yes.
أجل
Which counts you out.
مما يستبعدك
So why did you come to this office?
لمَ أتيتِ لمكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة إذاً؟
I--
...أنا
Mom...
...أمّي
You wanted to talk to the headmaster today.
أردتِ الكلام مع رئيس مجلس الإدارة الذي كان يُفترض به القدوم اليوم
Am I right?
ألستُ على حقّ؟
You are.
صحيح
I wanted Kenya to be a doctor like my late husband.
أردتُ أن يكون ابني كينيا طبيباً مثل زوجي الرّاحل
I wanted him to quit baseball.
فأردتُه أن يترك كرة القاعدة
I was going to ask the headmaster to take the team
كنتُ سأخبر رئيس مجلس الإدارة أنّي لم أرد مشاركته في البطولة
out of the tournament.
ليسحب الفريقَ منها
Unaware that he was going to do so anyway...
دون علمك أنّه كان سيأتي لإعلان الانسحاب بالأصل
Ironic, isn't it?
يا للسخرية
But he wasn't there, so you left.
لكنه لم يكن موجوداً، فغادرتِ المكتب
That's when Eto-kun saw you.
رآك إيتو-كن حينها
The hidden culprit then cut the flag.
مزّق الفاعل الحقيقيّ المختبئ وقتها العلم
But then Kaji-kun came in after he saw
لكنّ كاجي-كن دخل بعدما رآك
you in the window.
عبر النافذة وهو في الملعب
The culprit accidentally dropped the cutter,
أسقط الفاعل الشفرة في هربه هلعاً
which Kaji-kun picked up.
فالتقطها كاجي-كن
Certain that his mother had cut the flag,
معتقداً أنّ أمّه مزّقت علم البطولة
you two wound up covering for each other.
هكذا اندفعتما للتستّر على بعضكما
So who is the real culprit?
من الفاعل الحقيقيّ إذاً؟
One other person disappeared
يوجد هنا شخصٌ آخر قد أختفى
when his mother headed for the school.
عندما دخلت الأمّ المدرسة
A left-handed person less than 160 cm tall!
شخص أعسر وطوله يقلّ عن 160 سم
I'm referring to you...
...أنا أشير لك
No way!
مُحال
You don't mean--
...أيُعقل
Yes. The championship flag was cut
أجل، الفاعل الحقيقيّ الذي مزّق علم البطولة
by you, Principal!
!هو أنت أيّها الناظر
You waited for your chance to sneak in here
انتظرت فرصتك في التسلّل إلى هنا
before the headmaster was supposed to come.
وذلك قبل قدوم رئيس مجلس الإدارة
You snuck off after giving the impression
تسلّلت بعدما أعطيت انطباعاً للجميع
you were on the field, then cut the flag,
بأنك موجود في الملعب، ثمّ مزّقت العلم
made it look like someone broke in from outside,
وزيّفت قدوم شخص عبر النافذة من الخارج
and returned to the field.
ثمّ رجعت للملعب
That was your plan.
كانت هذه خطّتك
Pure conjecture! You have no proof!
!مجرّد افتراضات! لا دليل لديك
The key to this office should be in your pocket.
الدليل هو مفتاح مكتب رئيس مجلس الإدارة الموجود في جيبك
You intended to lock the door and return the key
كنتَ تنوي إقفال الباب وإعادة المفتاح
to create your ruse,
،لإكمال حيلتك
but you couldn't with everyone coming and going.
لكنك لم تستطع مع دخول وخروج الجميع من المكتب
The key hasn't been returned yet,
لم يرجع المفتاح للمخزن بعد
which means it's only natural to think the culprit
ما يعني أنّ من المنطقيّ افتراض
still has it!
!أنّه بحوزة الفاعل
Bad news!
!أنباء سيّئة
We just got a call-- the headmaster is dead!
تلقّينا اتصالاً للتوّ، يبدو أنّ رئيس !مجلس الإدارة قد تُوفيّ
No... What have I done?!
لا يمكن... ما كان الهدف مما فعلتُه؟
The headmaster told me
أخبرني رئيس مجلس الإدارة
to keep the team from entering the tournament.
أن أمنع الفريق من المشاركة في البطولة
But it wasn't so easy with the media watching!
لكن لم يكن الأمر يسيراً مع أنظار الإعلام وأولياء الأمور
People would condemn us for dropping out
على هذا النحو، كان رئيس المجلس ليعلن عن انسحاب الفريق بنفسه
and ruining a great pitcher's career!
فتتضرّر صورة المدرسة أمام المجتمع بشكلٍ مباشر
"What kind of school would crush kids' dreams?!"
"أيّ مدرسة قد تسحق أحلام شبّان؟"
So to drop out and protect the school's name, I--
لذا حاولتُ حماية سمعة المدرسة على الأقلّ حتّى مع الانسحاب
I loved this school!
!فقد أحبّبتُ هذه المدرسة
Much more than the headmaster!
!أكثر بكثير من رئيس المجلس ذاك
You're both the same in the end--
أنتما متشابهان في النهاية
you crushed kids' dreams with your own two hands!
سحقتما أحلام الشبّان بأيديكم
You're right. I was a fool!
معك حقّ، كنتُ مغفلاً
Forgive me!
!سـ-سامحوني
The tournament began half a month later,
بدأت البطولة بعدها بنصف شهر
and Shuko Academy was in it too.
وشاركت أكاديمية شوكو
The tournament directors saw their passion for baseball.
رأى مسؤولو المسابقة شغفهم لكرة القاعدة
Strike!
!رمية
Kaji's pitching brings them closer and closer
...رمي كاجي يقود أكايمية شوكو لانتصارات تدريجياً
to the new championship flag.
نحو علم بطولة جديد
He's dead!
لا جدوى، إنّه ميت
Who's behind this?!
مكيدة من؟
I was watching the whole time!
وأمام أنظاري، من يكون؟
Shinichi! Are you there?
شينتشي! أنت هنا، صحيح؟
Shinichi?
...شينتشي
Are you back, Shinichi?
...رجعت... شينتشي
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Karaoke Box Murder Case."
جريمة قتل حجرة الكاراوكي
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Reindeer.
حيوان رنّة أحمر الأنف